const reactFacts = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "When was React first released?",
        answer: "In 2013"
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: "What is ReactJS?",
        answer: "Is a JavaScript Library used in web applications development to build interactive elements on a website"
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: "Is React a Framework?",
        answer: "No. According to the official documentation React is a lightweight Library."
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: "What is JSX?",
        answer: "JSX (JavaScript Syntax Extension) is a templating engine that allows the developer to write markup directly in their code."
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: "What company is behind React?",
        answer: "Meta (Facebook)"
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: "What are React Hooks?",
        answer: "Hooks are functions that let developers \"hook into\" React state and lifecycle features from function components."
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: "Can props be passed from children components to parent components?",
        answer: "No, React props can only be passed from top-level components to lower-level components."
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: "How popular is React among developers?",
        answer: "In 2021 ReactJS overtook jQuery to become the most popular JavaScript Library among software developers worldwide."
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: "Which websites are built with ReactJS?",
        answer: "Facebook, BBC, CNN, Uber Eats, Airbnb, Netflix, Dropbox, CloudFlare, Discord, Skype, Slack, PayPal."
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: "What is React JS' official website?",
        answer: "https://reactjs.org"
    }
]

export default reactFacts;